hello and welcome to this webinar on
您好，欢迎参加此在线讲座
composite builds with Gradle I'm Trisha
Gradle我是Trisha的复合材料构建
gee I work for JetBrains I'm the jet
我在JetBrains工作我是喷气机
range developer advocate
范围开发者拥护者
mostly for IntelliJ IDEA and I'm joined
主要用于IntelliJ IDEA，我也加入了
by Stefan irma from Gradle hey hiding a
来自Gradle的Stefan irma嘿藏着
loop then I'm doing okay yeah I'm
循环然后我做得很好，是的，我
surviving so our plan for this webinar
幸存下来，所以我们这次网络研讨会的计划
is and Soufan will go through sort of
是，Soufan将经历
what composite builds are the purpose of
哪些复合材料的目的是
them and give a demo and then after that
他们，并给一个演示，然后在那之后
I'll give a demo of how this looks in
我将演示它的外观
IntelliJ IDEA 2017 point one and for our
IntelliJ IDEA 2017第一点针对我们
listeners there is an area in
听众中有一个区域
GoToWebinar where you can ask questions
GoToWebinar，您可以在其中提问
so you can ask questions as we go along
这样您可以在我们进行的过程中提出问题
I will try and field them and then I
我会尝试将它们放置，然后我
will I'll read them out and then perhaps
我会把它们读出来，然后也许
we can have some answers on on the air
我们可以播出一些答案
as we go so we'll try and find
随着我们的前进，我们将尝试找到
appropriate places for it and there will
合适的地方，那里
probably be a chance at the end to
可能是最后的机会
follow up on any other questions which
跟进其他问题
haven't been answered so far so without
到目前为止还没有得到答案
further ado let's dive straight in over
事不宜迟，让我们直接深入
to you oh thanks for so at Gradle were
谢谢你，谢谢Gradle的帮助
all about developer productivity and it
关于开发人员生产力及其一切的一切
turns out that this is not just about
事实证明，这不只是关于
making the build system itself fast
使构建系统本身快速
there are a lot of processes during
在过程中有很多过程
development that can significantly slow
发展会大大减慢
developers them and one of those
开发他们和其中之一
processes that we've looked at is when
我们看过的过程是什么时候
you try to combine projects and try to
您尝试合并项目并尝试
work on other people code points when
当别人在代码点上工作时
you need to fix the bug so let's say you
您需要修复该错误，所以说您
have an application that uses the
有一个使用
library that developed by a token team
由令牌团队开发的库
and now you want to take the bug in
现在你想把这个bug
their library or at least debug it
他们的库或至少调试它
somehow what do you normally do or you
不知何故你通常会做什么？
check out that code you build it you
签出您构建它的代码
install it into your local repo you
将其安装到本地仓库中
change your build to use whatever
更改构建以使用任何内容
snapshot you just installed into your
您刚刚安装到快照中的快照
local repo
本地回购
and then we can finally use it which is
然后我们最终可以使用它
a pretty annoying flow around and then
相当烦人的流量然后
for every little change that you try to
您尝试的每一个小变化
do for that library you have to install
为该库做您必须安装
it again and then try it out in your
再次尝试，然后在
code so the repository structure really
代码，因此存储库结构确实
dictates developer experience and this
决定开发人员的经验，这
this pain has led a lot of people to
这种痛苦导致很多人
move more towards big monolithic wood
向大型整体木材移动
batteries because it's just more
电池，因为它更多
convenient you can work with all your
您可以方便地与您一起工作
project at one arm when really in many
当很多时候真的伸出一只手臂
cases you would you would like to work
你想工作的情况
on small repository for modularity sake
在小型存储库上以实现模块化
for performance a just keeping your
为了表现只是保持您的
build small and also for for code
体积小，也用于代码
quality sake so it was really up until
优质的清酒，所以直到
now this problem that you had to make
现在，您必须要解决的这个问题
your choice basically either you
您的选择基本上就是
separated your project into a different
将您的项目分成不同的
repository and you use external
仓库，您使用外部
dependencies so like I've shown here the
依赖关系，就像我在这里展示的
dependencies compiled or my company and
依赖编译或我的公司和
so on which is deployed somewhere to
这样就可以部署到
your other factory or Nexus repository
您的其他工厂或Nexus存储库
and then you have this problem that I
然后你有这个问题，我
just outlined if you want to make a
只是概述了如果您想制作一个
little change you have to install it
小小的改变，你必须安装它
first and then change your bill to use
首先，然后更改您的账单以使用
that installed version versus if you put
安装的版本与您放置的版本
everything into one project you can use
一切都可以整合到一个项目中
project dependencies which gives you
项目依赖性
give you a fast workaround but it also
给您一个快速的解决方法，但是它也
tends to give you a large project that
往往会给你一个大项目
grows out of control pretty quickly so
很快失去控制，所以
this is what we try to what we try to
这就是我们试图做到的
fix with composite build so a couple the
使用复合材料构建解决方案
build are is very simply a combination
建立是非常简单的组合
of Gradle build you can include bills
您可以包括账单的Gradle版本
into other bills bills that are normally
变成其他通常正常的账单
independent of each other so developed
彼此独立，因此发达
by different teams and the binary
由不同的团队和二进制
dependencies from one project to another
从一个项目到另一个项目的依赖
are replaced with direct project
被直接项目取代
dependencies so as composite behaves as
依赖关系，因此复合材料表现为
if you had one big bill
如果你有一张大账单
containing all the projects as if you
包含所有项目，就好像您
had that mono repo and it allows you to
有那个单声道回购，它可以让你
do quick local experimentation allows
快速进行本地实验
you to import several bills together in
您要一起汇入几张账单
the IDE I think that Tricia will show
我认为Tricia将显示IDE
later and for instance to cross
以后例如越过
repository or factoring that what you
存储库或将您的因素考虑在内
need it allows you to smoothly migrate
需要它可以让您顺利迁移
from a monolith to a multi repo or maybe
从整体到多仓库，也许
even the other way around depending on
甚至反过来取决于
what you need and one of the coolest
您需要什么，也是最酷的之一
features for me personally the plugin
亲自为我提供的功能
developer is that this also works for
开发人员是，这也适用于
credit plugins so you can set the huge a
信用插件，因此您可以设置巨大的
plugin with a local version that you've
具有本地版本的插件
just checked out so what a further ado
刚刚退房，所以进一步
I'm going to show you what that means
我要告诉你那是什么意思
I'm on the command line and you'll
我在命令行上，您会
probably wonder hey where is IntelliJ
可能想知道IntelliJ在哪里
well I don't want to spoil everything
好吧，我不想破坏一切
so I'm just going to use a text editor
所以我将使用文本编辑器
here so let me just show you a very
在这里，让我向您展示一个非常
simple example of what I just explained
我刚刚解释的简单示例
we have an application which has
我们有一个应用程序
dependencies on two libraries that are
对两个库的依赖
written number you tools and string you
书面号码，您使用的工具和字符串，
tools and when I go into the application
工具以及我进入应用程序的时间
I'll actually find that I can't even
我会发现我什至不能
build it because those libraries are not
之所以建立它，是因为这些库不是
on J Center which I've listed as a
在我列为
repository and I also don't have them
仓库，我也没有
installed locally so if I say Gradle
在本地安装，所以如果我说Gradle
please assemble this it's going to fail
请组装它会失败
and say hey I can't I can find those
说嘿我找不到
dependencies so now I could go and um go
依赖关系，所以我现在可以去
into the my new tools project that has
进入我的新工具项目
also checked out and I could install it
还签出，我可以安装它
into my local repository and then I
到我的本地存储库中，然后我
could change my main build to use the
可以更改我的主要版本以使用
local repositories I could write
我可以写的本地存储库
something like that seems maven local
这样的东西似乎是本地的Maven
and then I could change my dependency
然后我可以改变我的依赖
declarations to let's say 1.1 snapshot
声明1.1快照的声明
and so on and so forth which is pretty
等等等等，这很漂亮
annoying but what it can do
烦人但它能做什么
that is Cal Gradle hain assemble this
那是Cal Gradle hain组装的
and just imagine that this other build
试想一下，这另一种构建
as my util is part of my gold
因为我的效用是我的金子的一部分
so maybe dad you'll see that Gradle
所以也许爸爸你会看到Gradle
doesn't just build my app but is also
不仅可以构建我的应用，还可以
built my evil and it was exactly the
建立了我的邪恶，这正是
project that I needed and if I just say
我需要的项目，如果我只是说
Gradle show me the dependencies for the
Gradle告诉我
compiled configuration then you'll see
编译的配置，那么您将看到
that I replaced number utils 100 with
我将数字utils 100替换为
the project my new tools number usuals
该项目我的新工具编号通常
so it's just behave as if I had included
所以就像我把
number new tools into my app so this is
将新工具编号到我的应用中，所以这是
really useful for quick local
对快速本地化非常有用
experimentation and actually this build
实验，实际上是这个版本
has a bug so let's say Gradle run and
有一个错误，所以说Gradle运行
your feed says oh 19 plus 23 equals 437
您的供稿说哦19加23等于437
unlikely so let's look what happened
不太可能，所以让我们看看发生了什么
here in our numbers class oh yeah I made
在我们的数字课上，是的，我做了
a simple mistake let's fix that and tell
一个简单的错误，让我们修复并告诉
Gradle to build again and you can see
再次构建Gradle，您可以看到
immediately not number you tools and
立即不给您的工具编号，
only number your tools is build again
仅编号您的工具可以再次构建
and my app behaves correctly so this is
我的应用程序行为正常，所以这是
in a nutshell what comforts are all
简而言之，什么都是舒适
about you can build your main
关于你可以建立你的主要
application and include other builds to
应用程序并包括其他构建
substitute dependencies so now you might
替换依赖项，所以现在您可能
not want to write this - - include build
不想写这个--包括构建
every time or you might want to make
每次或您可能想制作
that a little more persistent you can do
你可以做的更持久一些
that in settings or griddle so for
在设置或平板炉中
instance you could just write include
你可以写的实例包括
built in my you tools but that might not
内置在您的工具中，但可能不会
be the greatest idea because my app is
最好的主意，因为我的应用是
supposed to be a self-contained project
应该是一个独立的项目
so if you check that in
因此，如果您签入
to your repository then your see able to
到您的存储库中，然后您就能看到
probably start sailing saying well I can
大概开始说我可以
find my util it's not at all flash
找到我的实用程序，它不是一闪而过的
manuals but luckily perfect upgrade or
手册，但幸运的是，升级或
just a normal Gradle file or you can
只是一个普通的Gradle文件，或者您可以
write a little bit of predictors and say
写一些预测变量然后说
hey if my neutrals exist stem included
嘿，如果我的中立人存在
so it can basically create a dynamic
因此基本上可以创建一个动态
composite that just reacts to the local
只是对本地做出反应的复合材料
developer environment it has if you
如果您拥有开发人员环境
check out both of them then I'm going to
看看他们两个然后我要
compile against that you can also opt to
根据您也可以选择编译
not change your app at all and is that I
根本不改变您的应用程序，是我
have a third project that includes both
有第三个项目，包括
of them so this composite project that
他们这样的复合项目
I've created here it's really just there
我在这里创建它真的就在那里
to include both my app and my utils and
包括我的应用程序和工具
the result would be the same so could go
结果将是相同的，所以可以去
there and say Gradle run without having
在那里说Gradle不用跑
to specify any included bills because
指定任何包含的账单，因为
they persisted in the settings file and
他们保留在设置文件中，
you see it builds both my you tools and
您会看到它构建了我自己的工具和
my app and construct result so this
我的应用程序和构造结果
allows you to combine those really
可以让您真正结合
flexibly after opening the more
开后更灵活
elaborate example just a quick point is
详尽的例子只是一个快速点
it possible to increase the size of your
可能会增加您的尺寸
command line a little bit I'm sure a
命令行一点我确定
better I think it's better I'll find out
更好，我认为这会更好
if if there's any more queries on it but
如果还有其他查询，但是
looks better to me okay thanks cool so I
对我来说看起来更好，谢谢，很酷，所以我
said before that this also works for
之前说过，这也适用于
plugin development all so I like to
插件开发全部，所以我喜欢
develop Gradle plugins and so do many of
开发Gradle插件，许多
you I guess so let's look at that I go
你我想，所以让我们来看一下
into the plugin deaf project and into
进入插件聋人项目并进入
the consumer perfect so I'm going to
完美的消费者，所以我要
look at the project that's using my
看看正在使用我的项目
plugin and I've actually edited as an
插件，而我实际上已将其编辑为
included tool here so this is typically
此处包含工具，因此通常
what you do when you develop a plug-in
开发插件时的操作
and in the same repository you have a
在同一个存储库中，您有一个
few examples that your users can
您的用户可以举几个例子
get to figure out how to use your point
弄清楚如何使用你的观点
and traditionally what you had to do was
传统上您要做的是
install the plugin into local repository
将插件安装到本地存储库
and then try out the example now you can
然后现在尝试示例
just use a couple the bills so in mine
就用几张账单
consumer project I say Gradle greet
我说Gradle的消费者项目
because it was about a preteen porting
因为那是关于青春期的移植
and others I make and now if I go into
和我做的其他人，现在，如果我进入
my plugin and actually change the code
我的插件并实际更改代码
say well I'd like hey I like hello and
说好吧，我想嘿，我喜欢你好，
today Cradle Creed again I immediately
今天再次摇篮信条我立即
see the effect so I no longer have this
看到效果，所以我不再有这个
annoying turnaround I can just make
我可以做的烦人的转变
changes can i plug in and immediately
我可以立即插入更改
see what it does to the continuing
看看它对持续发展有什么作用
project so these are the most basic use
项目，所以这些是最基本的用途
cases on for a local developer to say I
案例让本地开发商说我
need to experiment with another project
需要尝试另一个项目
I need to experiment with a library that
我需要尝试一个图书馆
someone else has buildin which has a bug
别人的buildin里面有个bug
or I need to experiment that a plugin
或者我需要尝试一个插件
that somebody has built and it's not
有人建造的，不是
doing quite what I want but a couple of
做我想做的事，但有几个
those are also useful for a larger
这些对于更大的人也很有用
refactoring so for instance when you're
重构，例如当您
moving from n1 and reco to a multi repo
从n1和reco转移到多仓库
so currently all your projects are in
所以目前您所有的项目都在
one big repository and you'd like to
一个大的存储库，您想
split them apart um you had a bit of a
把它们分开，你有点
problem on your hand because if you just
你手上的问题，因为如果你只是
rip them apart and put them into
将它们撕开并放入
different repositories you're probably
您可能是不同的存储库
going to get into trouble because what
会陷入困境，因为
happens in one repo usually is that
发生在一个仓库中通常是
module reference each other in a very
模块相互引用
tangled way there's a lot of internal
纠结的方式有很多内部
API usage they should just split them
API使用情况，应将它们分开
apart and give them different release
分开给他们不同的释放
cycle what's probably going to happen is
周期可能会发生的是
that your app projects are constantly
您的应用程序项目不断
going to be broken by seemingly innocent
看起来天真无邪
changes in the libraries and then it
在库中进行更改，然后
turns out oh if internal API would
原来哦，如果内部API会
actually leave
实际离开
by one of the apps because they need to
通过其中一个应用程序，因为它们需要
be in one big model is where it was easy
在一个大模型中很容易
to to fix up internal API use issues so
解决内部API使用问题，以便
ideally you want to have a proper API
理想情况下，您希望拥有适当的API
before you split things apart but
在你把事情分开之前
enforcing this proper API split when
在以下情况下强制执行此适当的API拆分
everything is in one big build on
一切都建立在一个大的基础上
without any any boundaries can be pretty
没有任何界限可以很漂亮
hard so what kind of the build allows
很难，那么什么样的构建允许
you to do to say hey I'm going to stay
你要说的嘿我要留下来
inside my Lima logic repository but I'm
在我的Lima逻辑存储库中，但我在
going to take my project and already
要接受我的项目，已经
make them self-contained so I sort of
使它们自成一体，所以我有点
done here build a mono repo app and I
在这里完成构建一个单声道回购应用程序，我
pick a number you tools and a stream
选择您要使用的号码和信息流
utils project into its module folder and
utils项目进入其模块文件夹，然后
these two projects are completely
这两个项目是完全
self-contained so I could go into the
独立的，所以我可以进入
one repo module of number util sentence
一个数字util语句的回购模块
and say Gradle assemble and this project
说Gradle组装和这个项目
builds by itself so this is a this is a
本身建立，所以这是一个这是一个
completely self-sufficient Gradle
完全自给自足的Gradle
project I could import it into IntelliJ
我可以将其导入IntelliJ项目
for instance and say hey I just want to
例如说嘿，我只想
work on number you tools and nothing
使用数字工具而不是任何东西
else
其他
which will probably give me a faster ad
这可能会给我更快的广告
experience than importing my whole 500
经验比导入我的全部500
module mono repo and I could also
模块单声道回购，我也可以
install it for instance into my local
例如将其安装到我的本地
repository to use it later from another
存储库，以便以后在另一个存储库中使用
project but I can also use them together
项目，但我也可以一起使用
or what I've done here is I said in term
还是我在这里所说的
one repo settings Gradle file for every
每个仓库一个仓库设置Gradle文件
file in the module folder that is the
模块文件夹中的文件
directory include that as a book so
目录包括一本书，所以
number you to open string literals in
编号您要在其中打开字符串文字
that case and as you'll see on these
这种情况，您将在这些内容中看到
dependencies that my one repo app has
我的一个回购应用程序具有的依赖项
are binary dependencies
是二进制依赖项
so they reference the binary versions of
因此他们引用了
number which will sense from your tools
从您的工具中可以感觉到的数字
so on as I try to run I get same bug so
所以当我尝试运行时，我得到了相同的错误，所以
we're going to fix that in a minute
我们将在一分钟内解决该问题
and when I say Gradle give me the
当我说Gradle给我
dependencies of my mana repo up I can
我的法力回购依赖可以
see the replacement that I expect so
看到我期望的替代品
let's just fix that bug again this time
让我们这次再次修复该错误
here and again we'll keep doing the
在这里，我们将继续做
right thing and now I decide ok it's
对的事情，现在我决定好了
time to move number utils into its own
是时候将数字效用转移到自己的位置了
repository weeks fix everything up on
知识库周修复了所有问题
we're ready to publish it as its own
我们准备将其发布为自己的
standalone project and we're no longer
独立项目，我们不再
going to bundle it into our big mana
将其捆绑成我们的大魔法
repo it's it's going to be the first
回购这将是第一个
thing that we move somewhere else so
我们搬到其他地方的事情
let's move it somewhere else move number
让我们将其移动到其他位置
your tools somewhere else so now it'll
您的工具在其他地方，所以现在
no longer be found in the modules folder
不再在modules文件夹中找到
and when an SI try to run you'll see the
当SI尝试运行时，您会看到
pedal is no longer building number util
踏板不再是建筑编号工具
if it didn't pick it up and it's showing
如果没有捡起它并显示
above again because what it's using now
再次以上，因为它现在正在使用
is the room from my local repository
是我本地存储库中的房间
that I installed earlier you can see
我之前安装的您可以看到
string needles are still being replaced
线针仍在更换
with the string littles project whereas
与字符串littles项目，而
number.you tools is now coming from the
number.you工具现在来自
local repo and of course you can imagine
当地回购，您当然可以想象
this exactly the other way around
恰恰相反
um if I have several repositories but I
嗯，如果我有几个存储库，但是我
actually like to work with a mono repo
实际上喜欢与单声道回购合作
instead I should say um it's quite a big
相反，我应该说嗯，这很大
refactoring to make it all a single
重构使其全部成为单一
multi project built in one go I don't
一口气建立的多项目我不
really want to do that um I want to be
我真的很想做那个
more I want to go more step one so I'm
我想走更多第一步，所以我
just going to put all my bills that I
只是把我所有的账单
want to eventually make the project and
想要最终完成该项目，
put them into a folder in my mono repo
将它们放到我的单声道仓库中的文件夹中
and include them as incredible
并把它们包括在内
and they will behave much like
他们的行为会像
subprojects are put a little more
子项目再放一点
isolation and then I can take them one
隔离，然后我可以带他们一个
by one and convert them to actual
一并转换为实际
sub-project of my minoriko so equivalent
我的minoriko的子项目
would be I move from somewhere else to
我会从其他地方搬到
modules number you tools and then run so
模块编号您的工具，然后运行
that would be what I do if I was moving
那就是我要搬家时要做的
from multi repo to moderator so Gretel
从多重回购到主持人，所以Gretel
really makes teach keep borders between
真正使教导保持界限
one repo and multi ripple very fluent um
一个回购和多波纹非常流利
one last thing that I'd like to add as a
我想添加为最后一件事
really cool use case that several of the
真的很酷的用例
customers have already done is doing
客户已经做的就是做
this on pi/4 imagine you have your
pi / 4上的这个，想像你有
library team and your app team and your
库团队，您的应用团队以及您的
app team is using library version 1.2
应用团队正在使用库版本1.2
now they don't want to use snapshot
现在他们不想使用快照
because that's going to make their build
因为那将建立他们的
non reproducible and they don't want to
不可复制，他们不想
get any little box that the library team
得到图书馆小组的任何小盒子
might be introducing in between releases
可能会在两次发布之间引入
um they only want to have something
嗯，他们只想吃点东西
that's published but on the other hand
那已经出版了，但另一方面
the library team would really like to
图书馆团队真的很想
know whether the app will still work
知道该应用程序是否仍然可以运行
with their next release
与他们的下一个版本
so if the problem is to two forces that
因此，如果问题在于两种力量
and work here we're composite book you
在这里工作，我们是复合书
can do that really easily you just have
可以很轻松地做到这一点
a CI drop that checks out both the
CI引出线可同时检查
library and the app next to each other
库和应用程序彼此相邻
and includes them both into a composite
并将它们都合并到一起
and then just run all the tests from
然后从运行所有测试
third pane
第三窗格
yeah the app still works with the next
是的，该应用程序仍适用于下一个
main minor release of the library on so
该库的主要次要版本是这样
the library team instead of getting
图书馆团队而不是
feedback one month down the road when
反馈一个月的时间
the app teams finally upgrades to their
应用团队最终升级到他们的
next release and says oh yeah you broke
下一个版本，说哦，是的，你破产了
up they get feedback the same day from
他们在同一天就收到反馈
the CI server saying hey by the way
CI服务器说“嘿”
you're wonderfully upgrade is not binary
你很棒，升级不是二进制
compatible with one or two or you've
与一两个或您兼容
made a mistake you
弄错了你
okay so there are a few limitations
好，所以有一些限制
right now that I want to point out and
现在我想指出
which we're currently working on the
我们目前正在研究
first one is but right now you cannot
第一个是，但是现在你不能
target tasks and included those so what
目标任务并包括那些任务
that means is and my mama repo app I
这就是我的妈妈回购应用
currently cannot say Gradle on my
目前无法对我说Gradle
YouTube bill for instance um this is
YouTube帐单，例如，这是
something we'll fix our very soon
我们很快会解决的问题
actually
其实
we also currently don't support custom
我们目前还不支持自定义
publications so right now the
所以现在的出版物
substitution of project dependencies is
项目依赖项的替换是
completely based on project name and
完全基于项目名称和
project group RFPs mesh with the
项目组RFP与
dependency notation then it's replaced
依赖表示法，然后将其替换
with the project dependency if they
与项目相关，如果他们
don't then not we will expand this to
那就不，我们将其扩展到
work with the publishing plugins so that
使用发布插件，以便
we can replace multiple different arm
我们可以更换多个不同的手臂
dependency notations with projects are
项目的依赖项表示法是
included bills also aren't currently
包含的帐单目前也没有
executed in power that is also in the
在权力中执行
works already so that comes with bills
已经工作了，所以附有帐单
will be parallelized
将并行化
continuous build currently doesn't pick
连续构建当前未选择
up changes in included bills on this is
包括在这方面的账单上的变化是
going to be fixed it's not on the on the
将被修复，它不在
roadmap for the next month or so but
下个月的路线图，但
something we'll get around to for sure
我们肯定会解决的问题
we also currently don't support an
我们目前还不支持
effort composites so a composite that
努力复合体
includes another composite bill on but
包括另一项综合法案，但
again this is something that will
再次，这将是
definitely add something that's a little
肯定会添加一些东西
further out if at all is currently all
如果目前全部是更远的地方
boobs need to use the use the same
胸部需要使用相同的
Gradle version so the demon that used is
Gradle版本，所以使用的恶魔是
the one of the composite group project
综合小组项目之一
and all the included bills are run in
并且所有包含的账单都在
the same Gradle demon and using the same
相同的Gradle恶魔并使用相同的
Gradle version as a result so the last
结果是Gradle版本，所以最后
point was our boot camp so you might
关键是我们的新兵训练营，所以你可能
know that Gradle has a cloud service
知道Gradle有云服务
called
叫
Kem's that'll obviously to get deep
凯姆显然会变得更深
insight into what's going on in your
洞悉您的情况
build which transfer taking along etc
建立哪些转移进行等
and they currently don't support
他们目前不支持
composites or mostly because of how
复合材料或主要是因为
composites are wired up internally so um
复合材料内部连接起来，所以
where we want to go there is to make
我们想去的地方
them look exactly like a big multi
他们看起来就像一个大多
project build so you can see okay this
项目构建，这样您就可以看到
task came out of this build and a trip
任务来自这个构建和旅行
this long and it's one single task RAF
这么久，这是英国皇家空军的一项任务
Oh
哦
so that's also in the works yeah so um
所以这也在工作中
please follow along on the Gradle block
请按照Gradle块进行操作
um if you want to know more about
嗯，如果您想进一步了解
comfortable development we're going to
舒适的发展，我们要
invest a lot more into this feature in
在此功能上投入更多
the next three months and with that I'll
接下来的三个月，我将
hand it over to you Trish okay hopefully
希望能把它交给你
you can see my IntelliJ IDEA screen
您可以看到我的IntelliJ IDEA屏幕
quickly so I'm basically going to walk
很快，所以我基本上要走了
through the same examples that you walk
通过你走路的例子
through in from the command line and I'm
从命令行进入，我
going to show you so please support for
给你看，所以请支持
us to support in IntelliJ IDEA for the
我们为IntelliJ IDEA提供支持
same things it's probably the most
同样的事情可能是最
complicated one is the first one that
复杂的是第一个
we're going to set up this one doesn't
我们要设置的这个不
have any sort of automation so this
有任何自动化，所以这
shows the the kind of worst case
显示出最坏的情况
scenario where you have to set up
您必须设置的方案
everything manually so here and this is
手动进行所有操作，这是
the example that you had where you have
您所拥有的示例
a my app let's have a look at the main
我的应用程序让我们看一下主要
class and this is your main class which
这是你的主要课程
is dependent on on these two things here
在这里取决于这两件事
if we look at the build file we can see
如果我们查看构建文件，我们可以看到
these are the dependencies here and what
这些是这里的依赖以及什么
I wanted to do is I'll need to set up
我想做的是我需要设置
the composite build inside IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ IDEA内部的复合构建
so that it picks up these dependencies
这样就可以拾取这些依赖项
and allows you to navigate to the source
并允许您导航到源
for these dependencies so what we do is
这些依赖关系，所以我们要做的是
in our Gradle projects window which you
在我们的Gradle项目窗口中
can open by doing well a number of
可以通过做很多
different things either you can open it
不同的东西要么你可以打开它
from down here or you can open it from
从这里下来，也可以从
over here or what I cut often do is I
在这里或我经常剪的是我
use command II and I type Gradle and
使用命令II和I输入Gradle并
then I can see my Gradle window is
然后我可以看到我的Gradle窗口是
there let me close these down and so
在那里让我关闭这些，所以
what I'm going to do is I'm going to add
我要做的是添加
a new Gradle project to my project this
我的项目有一个新的Gradle项目
is going to be make sure I go to the
将确保我去
right place
正确的位置
I'm going to add build up Gradle from
我要从中添加构建Gradle
the my utils project make sure that I've
我的utils项目确保我已经
got the right version of Gradle and so
有正确版本的Gradle等
forth
向前
and then what I can do is I can set up
然后我可以做的就是设置
the composite build configuration inside
内部的复合构建配置
IntelliJ IDEA by right-clicking on the
右键单击IntelliJ IDEA
my app build and I can select my utils
我的应用程序构建，我可以选择我的工具
as the project that I'm going to include
作为我要包括的项目
in my composite builds so Gradle is
在我的复合建筑中，所以Gradle是
going to go away down here we build the
将要消失在这里，我们建立
project there we go so these are the
我们去的项目，所以这些是
these are the modules to include I
这些是要包括的模块
include those and I need to let's just
包括那些，我只需要
open this up here we see this isn't
在这里打开它，我们看到这不是
quite picked everything up so I'm just
捡了一切，所以我只是
going to refresh my Gradle projects
将刷新我的Gradle项目
whenever you're working in IntelliJ IDEA
每当您在IntelliJ IDEA中工作时
and you've made some changes to Gradle
并且您对Gradle进行了一些更改
and the changes that seems have been
似乎已经发生的变化
picked up the magic refresh button is
拿起魔术刷新按钮是
the thing which will usually make
通常会做的事情
everything work for you so you can see
一切对您都有效，所以您可以看到
down here we're doing a Gradle build
在这里，我们正在做一个Gradle构建
okay so hopefully what you can see as I
好吧，希望我能看到什么
press my refresh my magic refresh button
按我的刷新我的魔术刷新按钮
here on Gradle projects and now you can
在Gradle项目上，现在您可以
see that my app and has the dependencies
看到我的应用程序并具有依赖项
on the my utils modules as well and my
在我的utils模块上以及
main craft starts working so if I run
主要工艺开始工作，所以如果我跑步
this farm IntelliJ IDEA then we should
这个农场IntelliJ IDEA，那么我们应该
get an answer hmm okay interesting
得到答案嗯好吧有趣
oh I know I've done
哦，我知道我已经完成了
I'm going to I'm not going to delegate
我要去不代表
the IDE build to Gradle for this
IDE为此构建了Gradle
particular instance because I want to
特定的实例，因为我想
show it using the IDE build not Gradle
使用IDE构建而不是Gradle显示它
so when I run this it will it will run
所以当我运行它时它将运行
it and give me an answer now this is
它，给我一个答案，现在是
where we can see the navigation so
在这里我们可以看到导航
numbers dot add numbers is the thing
数字点加数字是东西
that we imported from sample number
我们从样品号导入的
utils we go to add and this is where we
utils，我们去添加，这是我们
can fix this to the plus for example
可以解决这个问题，例如
let's see that what we did is when we
让我们看看我们所做的是当我们
navigated some numbers we ended up
浏览了一些我们最终得出的数字
inside the my utils project and so we
在我的utils项目中，所以我们
can edit this file directly and then
可以直接编辑此文件，然后
when we rerun we should see the correct
当我们重新运行时，我们应该看到正确的
answer so then we get the correct answer
回答，那么我们得到正确的答案
and so now when we've got composite
所以现在当我们有了复合材料
bills and enabled in IntelliJ IDEA when
帐单并在IntelliJ IDEA中启用
I'm inside my app let's go back here oh
我在我的应用程序中，让我们回到这里哦
I'm already there I can do things like
我已经在那里，我可以做类似的事情
obviously I can navigate the code which
显然我可以浏览代码
is what we saw but we can also do things
是我们所看到的，但我们也可以做
like we can use the power of IntelliJ to
就像我们可以使用IntelliJ的功能
do things like renaming things and then
做诸如重命名的事情，然后
when I rename that then it's going to
当我重命名时，它将
rename the method in my in my library
重命名我库中的方法
code okay so that was kind of the most
代码还可以，所以这是大多数
difficult example because we have to
困难的例子，因为我们必须
manually add our dependency on a
手动添加我们对
different library code I what I'd like
我想要的是不同的库代码
to show is I'd like to show you some of
显示是我想给你看一些
the sort of hopefully more
希望更多
straightforward examples of importing
导入的简单示例
composite builds so one of the things we
复合材料的构建是我们要做的事情之一
can do let's let's import the different
可以让我们导入不同的内容
project
项目
so the the composite one that was demoed
所以合成的被演示的
earlier on from the command line if I
如果我较早从命令行
import this then IntelliJ IDEA should
导入此然后IntelliJ IDEA应该
pick up all of the dependencies that
拾取所有依赖项
were part of the Gradle composite build
是Gradle复合建筑的一部分
so I open this up it's picked up Java 9
所以我打开它，它拾起了Java 9
automatically by default which may give
默认情况下会自动
us some interesting results I'm going to
我们将得到一些有趣的结果
open up my Gradle window so now in the
打开我的Gradle窗口，现在在
Gradle window is still running some
Gradle窗口仍在运行
processes down on the bottom so the the
在底部进行处理，因此
the windows will be updated when that's
窗户将在
all finished but you can see that I have
全部完成，但你可以看到我有
a dependency on my app I have a
对我的应用程序有依赖性
dependency on my utils the number utils
对我的效用的依赖数
and I have my root as well so from the
我也有自己的根基
root for example here we go so here's
例如，我们在这里开始，所以
all the project data to import just
所有要导入的项目数据
accept the defaults that IntelliJ gives
接受IntelliJ提供的默认值
you and then you can see all of the the
你然后你可以看到所有的
code for the for all of the different
适用于所有不同代码
projects that we were dependent on so
我们所依赖的项目
when our our composite build.gradle file
当我们的复合build.gradle文件
had all of these included builds
具有所有这些包含的构建
IntelliJ found all of those builds and
IntelliJ找到了所有这些构建，
imported the code for those things as
将这些东西的代码导入为
well and then we can do things like it's
好，然后我们可以做类似的事情
in route for example we can run the the
在路线上，例如我们可以运行
build from there I really hope this
我真的希望从那里建立
works this time
这次工作
okay so then everything worked and when
好吧，那么一切都正常了，什么时候
you run things from when you run Gradle
您从运行Gradle时开始运行
tasks from inside IntelliJ IDEA you can
您可以从IntelliJ IDEA内部执行任务
either get it this a sort of familiar
要么让它有点熟悉
text output or you can get it as a sort
文本输出或您可以将其分类
of pretty green blob thing so you can
绿色斑点的东西，所以你可以
see exactly which things got them and
确切地知道是什么让他们得到的，
where any failures were or if anything
哪里有故障或有什么问题
was perhaps ignored for example
例如可能被忽略了
so that's IntelliJ IDEA ability to look
所以这是IntelliJ IDEA的外观
at all of these independent dependencies
所有这些独立的依赖
and pull in all the code for all the
并提取所有代码
projects is dependent on let's have a
项目取决于我们有一个
look at
看着
another example so if we look at let's
另一个例子，所以让我们看一下
close this one down import another one
关闭此一个导入另一个
so if we import our mono repo
所以如果我们导入我们的mono仓库
door window again so again we can see
再次打开门窗，所以我们可以看到
the the individual projects that were
个别的项目是
dependent on we can see when this is
取决于我们何时可以看到
finished indexing and so forth we'll see
完成索引编制等等，我们将看到
all of this come up properly and any
所有这些都正确地出现了
minute now we'll see these come in as as
分钟，我们将看到这些作为
IntelliJ modules there we go so these
我们去了IntelliJ模块
are the modules to import it stick them
是要导入的模块吗？
all up and it's picked all of those up
全部都捡起来了
from from these settings that we have
从这些设置中
from the Bill Gradle and from the
从Bill Gradle和
settings Gradle it's been able to pick
设置Gradle能够选择
up everything that's inside modules and
处理模块内部的所有内容，
import all of those as IntelliJ modules
将所有这些导入为IntelliJ模块
as well so again you get all the same
同样，再次得到相同的结果
things that you expect to be able to get
您期望能够得到的东西
you can rename you can navigate and and
您可以重命名，也可以浏览，然后
so forth so from an intelligence a point
以此类推
of view these composite builds just kind
看来这些复合材料建造得很好
of create the IntelliJ project that you
创建您的IntelliJ项目
expect to be able to work with so you
期望能够与您合作
can edit the file rename staff and so
可以编辑文件重命名人员等
forth the final example that I've got
第四，我得到的最后一个例子
was the was developing plugins this one
是当时正在开发的插件
also should work automatically I say the
也应该自动工作我说
word should but the first one should
单词应该，但第一个应该
have worked as well so if we open up
也很好，所以如果我们开放
plugins
外挂程式
I think the first one the only thing
我认为第一个是唯一的事情
that didn't work was actually running
没用的实际上正在运行
great attack so it might just be missing
伟大的攻击，所以它可能会丢失
the include built pavement for the thing
包括东西的人行道
that he configured in the UI Oh
他在UI中配置的哦
for running talk yes I think so that I
进行谈话是的，我想
was kind of surprised by that because I
对此感到惊讶，因为我
thought that was supposed to that was
以为应该是
supposed to work automatically and so
应该可以自动工作等等
I'm going to go away and have a have a
我要走了，有一个
look at that and and feed that back to
看一看，然后反馈给
our team as well
我们的团队也一样
oh so again while it's a it's still
哦，再说一遍，它仍然是
building and indexing and so forth here
在这里建立和索引等等
we have our build.gradle which has our
我们有我们的build.gradle有我们的
build script which is dependent upon
构建脚本取决于
this disk greeting plug-in let's say ok
这个磁盘问候插件，好吧
to all of this you'll see that IntelliJ
所有这些，您将看到IntelliJ
she brings in the code for the greeting
她输入了问候代码
plug-in even though what I did was I
插件，即使我所做的只是我
opened the project for the consumer and
为消费者打开了该项目，
it put it brought in the code for the
它把它带进了代码
greeting plug-in so if I run this and
问候插件，所以如果我运行这个
let's have a look at the consumer what
让我们来看看消费者
I'm going to do is I run greeked Bob so
我要做的就是跑招呼鲍勃，所以
I get hello Bob but if I wanted to
我向鲍勃问好，但如果我想
change the greeting task to say hi with
将问候任务更改为打招呼
a capital obviously and and get rid of
显然是资本，并且摆脱了
this here when I rerun obviously
当我重新运行时，这显然
IntelliJ IDE is indexing everything
IntelliJ IDE正在索引所有内容
because I've just created the new
因为我刚刚创建了新的
project let's try re running that so I
项目让我们尝试重新运行它，所以我
rerun and I get hi Bob
重新运行，我得到鲍勃
so again like am like a farmer saying
所以又像农夫说
this gives you the ability to work
这使您能够工作
directly with a project which is using a
直接与使用
plug-in but also change the details of
插件还能改变细节
the plug-in and see those see the
该插件，并看到那些看到
effects of those changes straight away
这些变化的影响马上
without having to rebuild whole things
无需重建整体
and like upload them into repositories
并喜欢将它们上传到存储库中
and so forth you can just work with the
依此类推，您可以使用
code as if it's a single codebase I
就像是我的单个代码库一样
think that's pretty much all I wanted to
认为这几乎就是我想要的
to demo so perhaps we can have a look
演示，也许我们可以看看
any questions is there anything else
任何问题还有其他
that you wanted to cover Lana very
你想涵盖拉娜
luscious are very cool to see that maybe
甜美很酷，看到也许
one thing to add is that um as you might
要添加的一件事是，
know Gradle maintains the great Eclipse
知道Gradle保持着出色的Eclipse
plugin called Bill chip which also have
名为Bill chip的插件也有
this support since version 2.0 now so
自2.0版以来的这种支持现在
what you just saw on IntelliJ importing
您刚刚在IntelliJ导入中看到的内容
composite works there what we don't have
复合材料在那里我们没有的东西
is a really sweet arm manual UI yep so
是一个非常可爱的手臂手动用户界面，所以
um composing builds using the user
um使用用户进行构建
interface instead of using settings but
界面而不是使用设置，但是
great all that's something that's a bit
太棒了，这有点
not yet offer
尚未报价
so basically whichever IDE you're using
所以基本上无论您使用哪个IDE
you get the support for composite builds
您可以获得复合材料构建的支持
GoPro and right I'm going to have a
GoPro，对，我要准备一个
quick look at the questions through here
快速浏览这里的问题
unfortunately a whole bunch of them are
不幸的是，其中有很多人
we just dropped the audio so I have to
我们只是放下音频，所以我必须
have a quick wade through that and let's
快速浏览一下，让我们
have a look so one of the questions was
看看，所以其中一个问题是
does this work does this work with the
这项工作与
dependency in the builds source project
构建源项目中的依赖
is that not the same as plugins or no
与插件不同还是没有
that's stuff that happens at the
那就是发生在
beginning before you only all right see
在你一切都好之前开始
all so the answer is no because the
所有的答案是否定的，因为
source is executed before the setting
设置之前执行源
script is executed so those sources
脚本已执行，因此这些源
quite special in that regard um so we
在这方面很特别，所以我们
can only tell what builds you have
只能告诉你你拥有什么
included after the flooding script has
包含在洪水脚本之后
been executed and build tours on execute
已执行并在执行时建立巡视
it before that ok another question does
在那之前，另一个问题呢
this work with configure on demand is it
按需配置这项工作是吗
that sounds like yes demos should work
听起来不错，演示应该可以工作
and here's a question about
这是一个关于
oh it's about Java 9 I'm not sure that's
哦，这是关于Java 9的，我不确定
a good topic or not how will Gradle
一个好话题与否，Gradle将如何发展
composite builds work with pixel modules
复合构建与像素模块一起使用
in Java 9 is there already a plan for
在Java 9中已经有一个计划
supporting it um not really related to
支持它，而不是真正与
chips or module second um so
芯片或模块秒
comfortable the ridge is the way to
舒适的山脊是通往
break either break down a big build into
分解或分解成大块
smaller goals or on combine the hopes to
较小的目标或合并希望
work on different ones in the same idea
以相同的想法处理不同的人
session on the same of the I build on
会话与我建立的相同
clicks all is much more on the on the
点击所有的就更多了
Gradle project level like on single
摇篮项目级别像单
sub-project defining API and
子项目定义API和
implementation dependencies defining API
实现依赖定义API
and implementation packages so we with
和实施包，所以我们
Gradle through it for we already added
通过摇篮，因为我们已经添加了
the ability to split your API
拆分API的能力
implementation dependencies and we will
实现依赖，我们将
look into deeper java 9 support and this
深入研究Java 9支持
year so we will add support for defining
年，因此我们将增加对定义的支持
what your api packages are and then
您的api包是什么，然后
either generating a module descriptor or
生成模块描述符或
maybe reading the information from the
也许从中读取信息
module descriptor that's not entirely
模块描述符不完全是
signed yet iff it's rather unrelated to
已签名，但前提是它与
competence I'll work on it I have a
我会胜任的能力
whole bunch of questions around Java 9
有关Java 9的全部问题
in Gradle but I think that's probably
在Gradle中，但我认为可能是
slightly off topic
稍微偏离主题
I'm sorry more around my own personal
对不起，我对自己的看法更加抱歉
pain points and the general answer is on
痛点和一般答案是
credit cards we doesn't run on jigsaw
我们不会在拼图上运行的信用卡
because there have been changes over
因为发生了变化
changes every time we tried and we felt
每次尝试都会改变，我们感到
ok now we run on jigsaw or there was
好吧，现在我们在拼图上运行，或者有
another nightly bill to keep some other
另一份每晚账单
purpose again ah so we postponed that
再次有目的啊，所以我们推迟了
for a while to stop shaking the rabbit
暂时停止摇动兔子
but we will get back to it in April and
但是我们会在四月回到
to the absolute minimum is running on
到绝对最小值
jigsaw and then we'll see about the next
拼图，然后我们将了解下一个
steps for instance um building modular
例如um构建模块化的步骤
apps and defining your your API ok and
应用程序并定义您的API，然后
yeah I mean I definitely experienced the
是的，我的意思是我绝对经历了
fact that obviously Java 9 isn't out yet
Java 9显然尚未发布的事实
so a lot of the lot of the early access
所以很多的早期访问
build were very much as exchanging
建立就像交换
work-in-progress
工作正在进行中
absolutely um I have a question
绝对嗯，我有一个问题
how about including a second level
包括第二层怎么样
dependency I think you might have
依赖，我想你可能有
covered that in the limitations
涵盖了局限性
oh no no it doesn't matter um if it's a
哦，不，这不重要吗
transitive dependency order of
的传递依存顺序
dependency any dependency can be
任何依赖都可以是
replaced with
替换为
a project from an incredible so this
一个不可思议的项目，所以这
doesn't just work for first level
不仅适用于第一级
dependencies that you explicitly editing
您明确编辑的依赖项
descriptives works for any transitive
描述性词适用于所有传递词
dependency and this even works like if
依赖，甚至像
you have in another included bills a
您在其他包含的帐单中
dependent a binary dependency that can
依赖二进制可以
be supplied by yet another included
由另一个提供
growth that will all be replaced so
增长将全部被取代
completely integrated into the
完全整合到
dependency resolution engine cool so you
依赖解析引擎很酷，所以您
can basically use it more or less where
基本上可以或多或少地使用它
you expect to the ideas of dependency go
你期望依赖的想法去
through and we're in the related
通过，我们在相关
question can I use this to replace jar
问题我可以用它代替罐子吗
dependencies from flat their
从他们的依赖
repositories good question and flatly
仓库好问题，断然
repair it you usually don't have a group
修理它，你通常没有一个小组
so that might not work
这样可能不起作用
I have to I would have to try and we
我必须尝试，而我们
don't have that case for that right I
我没有那个案子
think this might be the same question is
认为这可能是相同的问题是
the second level dependency question
第二级依赖问题
this is my project a has dependency on
这是我的项目，对
spring which has a dependency on Commons
依赖公共的春天
logging can I include comments logging
我可以记录评论吗
on as a composite dependency ago yeah
作为复合依赖之前
loads more questions about audio being
加载有关音频存在的更多问题
off half will have found be captured in
一半将被捕获
the webinar replay and no I don't think
网络研讨会重播，不，我不认为
so because I lost sound as well and I'm
因为我也失去了声音，所以我
recording the webinar so what we will
录制网络研讨会，以便我们做些什么
try and do is take a quick look at at
尝试做的是快速浏览一下
the video and see if perhaps we can edit
视频，看看我们是否可以编辑
it so that at least we don't have big
这样，至少我们没有大的
gaps where we're losing sound so will
差距，我们正在失去声音，所以会
perhaps chop those out and and stitch
也许把那些切碎然后缝起来
them back together any special
他们一起回到任何特别的地方
requirements set up for Gradle wrapper
为Gradle包装器设置的要求
um but not quite clear what the question
嗯，但不清楚
of and okay I don't have any more
好的，我没有了
information so if the person who wrote
信息，如果写信的人
that question can perhaps add a bit more
这个问题也许可以增加更多
detail that'd be really useful yeah
细节真的很有用
okay still loads of things about missing
好吧，还有很多关于失踪的事情
sound um I'll go sort this out obviously
听起来很好，我会去解决这个问题
have you have you enabled the composite
你有没有启用复合
build in Gradle project section I think
我认为在Gradle项目部分构建
that was when I was doing my demo and I
那是我做演示的时候，我
think I showed that I enabled comfort
以为我表明我使自己感到舒适
builds okay and people suggesting I
建立好，有人建议我
invalidate caches and restart that was a
使缓存无效并重新启动那是一个
very useful suggestion and if we wanted
非常有用的建议，如果我们愿意
to be able to use delegate to build one
能够使用委托来建立一个
today to Gradle what would we need to do
今天要Gradle我们需要做什么
is setting up Gradle include build and
正在设置Gradle include build和
either either should work so I think
两者都应该工作，所以我认为
what we saw on the demo was a buck in
我们在演示中看到的是
the run Gradle task when you use the
使用时运行Gradle任务
composite configuration UI that didn't
没有的复合配置用户界面
work I'm sure Trisha yes in office work
我确定Trisha是办公室工作
and it already worked for Bill defined
它已经为Bill定义了
with setting per Gradle so it should
与每个Gradle的设置，所以它应该
feel transparently work it should yes
感觉工作透明，应该
and the delegate builds run to Gradle
和委托构建运行到Gradle
and all of the stuff should work for
所有的东西都应该为
both whether you're running it from
无论您是否从
Gradle inside the IDE whether you're
在IDE内摇篮无论您是否
running the IDE build or whether you're
运行IDE版本或是否正在运行
delegating the IDE build to the Gradle
将IDE构建委托给Gradle
build there as you saw there were some
如你所见，在那里建立
much we call them opportunities for
我们称他们为
improvement and and as I said you know
改善，正如我所说，您知道
this is a this is an early access and
这是一个抢先体验，
this is kind of good news for us because
这对我们来说是个好消息，因为
as we find these problems it means that
当我们发现这些问题时，这意味着
we can fix them before release so all of
我们可以在发布前修复它们，因此所有
this should work seamlessly in terms of
这应该在以下方面无缝地工作
whether you run it from Gradle whether
是否从Gradle运行它
you run it from the IDE whether you
无论您是否从IDE运行它
delegate the ide builds Gradle is CLI
代表ide构建Gradle是CLI
support for composite going to be
支持复合材料
included in near minor releases and up
包含在几乎次要版本中
on the table some prattle for each one
在桌子上，每个人都喝一口
can you run in debug mode and step into
您可以在调试模式下运行并进入
code that's in an included build
包含的版本中的代码
absolutely that's very much part of the
绝对那是
point so if you're debugging and you've
指出，因此，如果您要调试并且
got breakpoints inside an included
在其中包含断点
project then you should be able to stop
项目，那么您应该能够停止
at those breakpoints and so would build
在那些断点处，所以会建立
source work if you added a composite
如果添加了复合材料，则源工作
build in the build source settings
在构建源设置中构建
Gradle someone really wants to get
摇篮某人真的想得到
special
特别
that's a valid point absolutely it might
这绝对是一个有效的观点
I haven't tried to be quite honest I
我还没说实话
haven't tried on my fail give it a try
没有尝试过我的失败尝试一下
and open the bug if it doesn't please do
如果没有请打开错误
composit builds work for swapping out
合成构建工作以换出
plugins with both the old apply syntax
具有旧的Apply语法的插件
and the new plug-in syntax or only the
和新的插件语法或仅
new syntax unfortunately only with the
不幸的是，新语法仅适用于
old build scripts syntax at the moment
目前的旧版构建脚本语法
because the new reporting syntax is
因为新的报告语法是
based on special publications special
根据特别出版物特别
so-called plug-in markers and compatible
所谓的插件标记和兼容
do not yet support custom publications
尚不支持自定义出版物
which is why does feature is super high
这就是为什么功能超高的原因
priority to fix three months if there
如果有的话，优先修复三个月
are tool available to commit changes
可用于提交更改的工具
once that commits get to their separate
一旦提交到他们分开
repos I used ink string utils and number
回购我使用了墨水字符串utils和number
utils so I believe the question here is
utils，所以我相信这里的问题是
in the project supers got one open I
在项目中超级有一个开放我
don't have one open but let's say I make
没有一个开放但我说
changes to the greeting plug-in and I
更改为问候插件，我
make changes to the consumer if I do a
如果我做一个改变消费者
commit inside IntelliJ IDEA will let
在IntelliJ IDEA内部提交将使
commit those changes to the to the
将这些更改提交到
individual different repos no you have
个别不同的仓库，你没有
to commit to you have to commit each one
承诺你必须承诺每个
individually to their own repos
单独给自己的仓库
I believe I haven't tried that but when
我相信我还没有尝试过
I'm working with multi repo projects I
我正在与多个仓库项目合作
usually manually make sure that I I
通常手动确保
commit each set of changes to the
将每组更改提交给
correct repo will this work with
正确的回购将与
configuration stuck all that resolution
配置卡住了所有分辨率
strategy fail on version conflict is a
策略因版本冲突而失败是
composite included in a library that
包含在库中的复合
complies with another dependency I don't
符合我不依赖的另一个依赖
know what that means do you know what
知道什么意思你知道什么
that means
那意味着
okay well it's work with configurations
好吧，它可以与配置一起使用
like a fellow version conflict as a
就像同伴版本冲突一样
composite included a library that
复合材料包括一个库
collides with another dependency
与另一个依赖冲突
no because dependency substitutions are
否，因为依赖替换是
not based on the version so a project
不是基于版本，所以一个项目
dependency is only identified by
依赖关系仅由
exclusive name so it won't actually
专有名称，因此实际上不会
collide or it'll just be the product
碰撞，否则将只是产品
we will just be you okay
我们会没事的
and only should work with oh this is a
只能与它一起使用哦，这是一个
greater rapper clarification all these
说唱歌手更加清晰
should work with Gradle rapper without
应该与Gradle说唱歌手一起使用
any change to the build script correct
对构建脚本的任何更改均正确
yes and I highly recommend everybody to
是的，我强烈建议大家
use the Gradle wrapper and all their
使用Gradle包装器及其所有
projects yeah I'm a massive fan of the
是的，我是
grader app I don't have to worry about
我不必担心的评分应用程序
which version of Gradle am using it is
正在使用哪个版本的Gradle
flex hopefully and have you tried this
希望弯曲，你尝试过这个吗
as git submodules
作为git子模块
if yes was it totally seamless get some
如果是的话，那是完全无缝的吗？
modules is certainly like very close to
模块当然非常接近
the modules folder that I showed in the
我在中显示的modules文件夹
moderator example um I personally don't
主持人示例嗯，我个人不
have much experience with get sub
在获取子项方面有很多经验
modules to be honest but if you're using
说实话的模块，但如果您使用的是
sub modules
子模块
you know without like leaving out Gradle
你知道而不必放弃Gradle
just if you were successfully using git
就算您成功使用了git
submodules in general or that gif
一般子模块或该gif
teacher it works well for you then
老师，那对你很好
composite build should work well so you
复合版本应该可以正常工作，所以您
would just use a for loop for instance
例如只会使用for循环
to iterate over your sub modules folder
遍历子模块文件夹
and include those thoughts great that
并包括那些很棒的想法
looks like all the questions that we've
看起来像我们所有的问题
got hopefully we'll be able to write up
希望我们能够写出来
the answers to those questions and
这些问题的答案，以及
perhaps include them in a blog post or
也许将它们包含在博客文章中，或者
keep them on the end of this video as I
像我一样把它们放在本视频的结尾
said before this video will be available
在此视频可用之前说
probably in a few days time and will be
大概几天后，将会
publicly available thank you so much for
公开感谢您非常感谢
Han forum for demoing composite builds
Han演示组合物构建论坛
or more open view and yes so thanks
或更开放的视野，是的，谢谢
everybody and goodbye yeah
大家再见